breakfast in bed what's the occasion
nothing we just wanted to do something
for you for a change because
it's true we really need you
you drive us to school in bad weather
they need me you're always able to put
food on the table you put broken things
back together
it's true we really need you
and the more they need you the more you
need prudential prudential the rock
when other people count on you you need
something to count on even if you're not
around anymore for one out of four
insured americans that something is a
piece of the rock
you'll get us close summer vacations
[Music]
and the more they need you the more you
need prudential for life health auto
home get a
piece
insurance